<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LoveIn</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start</string>
    <string name="partners_name">Partner\'s name</string>
    <string name="add_partner">Add partner</string>
    <string name="erogenous_zones">Erogenous zones</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear all</string>

    <string name="not_enough_partners_alert_title">Not enough partners</string>
    <string name="not_enough_partners_alert_description">To begin exploring erotic zones, you will need at least 2 partners.</string>
    <string name="add_partner_name_alert_title">Add partner name</string>
    <string name="add_partner_name_alert_description">To start exploring erotic zones, you need to add your partner\'s name.</string>
    <string name="add_partner_ero_zones_alert_title">Add erogenous zones</string>
    <string name="add_partner_ero_zones_alert_description">To begin exploring erogenous zones, you need to add erogenous zones for each partner.</string>

    <string name="scalp_and_hair">Scalp and Hair</string>
    <string name="ears">Ears</string>
    <string name="navel">Navel</string>
    <string name="lower_stomach">Lower stomach</string>
    <string name="small_of_the_back">Small of the back</string>
    <string name="armpits">Armpits</string>
    <string name="inner_arms">Inner arms</string>
    <string name="inner_wrist">Inner wrist</string>
    <string name="palm_of_hands_and_fingertips">Palm of hands and fingertips</string>
    <string name="behind_the_knee">Behind the knee</string>
    <string name="nipples">Nipples</string>
    <string name="lips">Lips</string>
    <string name="neck">Neck</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh">Inner thigh</string>
    <string name="bottom_of_feet_and_toes">Bottom of feet and toes</string>
    <string name="anus">Anus</string>
    <string name="buttocks">Buttocks</string>

    <string name="glans">Glans</string>
    <string name="scrotum_and_testicles">Scrotum and testicles</string>
    <string name="perineum">Perineum</string>
    <string name="prostate">Prostate</string>
    <string name="penis">Penis</string>

    <string name="areola_and_nipples">Areola and nipples</string>
    <string name="pubic_mound">Pubic mound</string>
    <string name="clitoris">Clitoris</string>
    <string name="g_spot">G-spot</string>

    <string name="scalp_and_hair_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s scalp. Apply light pressure, adjusting the speed and intensity to your partner\'s preferences. Then, use the pads of your fingers to massage the scalp in circular motions for 1–3 minutes.</string>
    <string name="scalp_and_hair_scratch_action">%, lightly scratch %\'s scalp. Start at the nape and move towards the forehead, then from the ears to the crown. Adjust the speed and pressure to enhance the sensation.</string>
    <string name="scalp_and_hair_pinch_action">%, gently pinch %\'s scalp. Move from the nape to the forehead and from the ears to the crown while maintaining a light pinching motion to stimulate your partner further.</string>
    <string name="scalp_and_hair_pull_action">%, run your fingers through %\'s hair and gently pull.</string>
    <string name="scalp_and_hair_use_accessories_0_action">%, gently comb %\'s hair using a soft or wide-toothed comb. Slow, rhythmic strokes can enhance the pleasurable sensations.</string>
    <string name="scalp_and_hair_use_accessories_1_action">%, enhance sensory experiences by applying scented hair products, such as oils or perfumes, to %\'s scalp and hair.</string>
    <string name="scalp_and_hair_use_accessories_2_action">%, use a special scalp massager to help % relax and enjoy additional stimulation.</string>
    <string name="scalp_and_hair_blow_warm_air_action">%, gently blow warm air onto %\'s scalp and hair. This can promote relaxation and add an extra layer of arousal.</string>
    <string name="ears_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s earlobes using light pressure and small circular motions to enhance sensitivity.</string>
    <string name="ears_whisper_action">%, whisper tender words to %. The ears are rich in nerve endings and can be so sensitive that even a soft whisper can trigger arousal.</string>
    <string name="ears_bite_action">%, gently nibble on %\'s earlobes to elicit pleasurable sensations.</string>
    <string name="ears_kiss_action">%, gently kiss %\'s earlobes and the area around the ear. This can deepen arousal and create unforgettable sensations.</string>
    <string name="ears_suck_action">%, softly suck on %\'s earlobes to enhance arousal and explore new sensations.</string>
    <string name="ears_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to gently trace the outer contours of %\'s ears, following their natural shape.</string>
    <string name="ears_ice_action">%, use an ice cube to awaken the nerve endings in %\'s earlobes. Gently glide it along the contours of the ears to heighten stimulation and arousal.</string>
    <string name="navel_kiss_action">%, gently kiss %\'s belly button and the surrounding area to evoke pleasurable sensations and arousal.</string>
    <string name="navel_lick_action">%, gently lick %\'s belly button, playfully teasing the surrounding area with your tongue.</string>
    <string name="navel_blow_warm_air_action">%, blow warm breath on %\'s belly button, creating a gentle sensation of warmth and awakening the erogenous nerves.</string>
    <string name="navel_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory. Glide it over the skin around %\'s belly button to spark arousal and pleasant sensations. Light, teasing strokes can feel incredibly sensual.</string>
    <string name="navel_ice_action">%, gently run an ice cube around %\'s belly button. The chill enhances sensitivity and awakens erogenous nerves.</string>
    <string name="lower_stomach_kiss_action">%, gently kiss the lower part of %\'s abdomen to spark soft, sensual sensations.</string>
    <string name="lower_stomach_lick_action">%, gently lick the lower part of %\'s abdomen, moving from the navel down to the pubic mound. This can awaken deeper arousal and bring new sensations.</string>
    <string name="lower_stomach_massage_action">%, gently massage the lower part of %\'s abdomen using circular motions, light pressure, or soft pinches. Use oil or lotion to enhance stimulation and arousal.</string>
    <string name="lower_stomach_scratch_action">%, delicately run your nails over %\'s lower abdomen, evoking a slight tension that heightens arousal.</string>
    <string name="lower_stomach_blow_warm_air_action">%, gently blow warm breath on the lower part of %\'s abdomen, creating a soothing warmth that awakens the senses.</string>
    <string name="lower_stomach_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to caress %\'s lower abdomen. Gentle, teasing strokes can evoke deep pleasure and arousal.</string>
    <string name="lower_stomach_ice_action">%, gently glide an ice cube over the lower part of %\'s abdomen. The chill can amplify sensation and arousal.</string>
    <string name="areola_and_nipples_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s areolas and nipples. Use light circular motions, pinches, and gentle pressure to bring your partner new and exciting sensations. Oils or lotions can enhance the softness and sensuality of the massage.</string>
    <string name="areola_and_nipples_kiss_action">%, gently kiss %\'s areolas and nipples.</string>
    <string name="areola_and_nipples_suck_action">%, gently suck on %\'s nipples, alternating with soft licks or kisses to enhance stimulation and arousal.</string>
    <string name="areola_and_nipples_lick_action">%, gently lick %\'s areolas and nipples. Playful licking and soft kisses can be especially arousing.</string>
    <string name="areola_and_nipples_bite_action">%, gently nibble or lightly bite %\'s nipples and areolas. Pay close attention to your partner\'s reaction and adjust the pressure to ensure it stays pleasurable.</string>
    <string name="areola_and_nipples_use_accessories_0_action">%, use special toys to stimulate %\'s areolas and nipples. Small vibrators, clitoral stimulators, or nipple clamps with adjustable pressure can intensify sensations and arousal.</string>
    <string name="areola_and_nipples_use_accessories_1_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to caress %\'s areolas and nipples. Gentle strokes can feel incredibly arousing.</string>
    <string name="areola_and_nipples_ice_action">%, use an ice cube to stimulate %\'s areolas and nipples. Gently glide it over and around the nipples to evoke new sensations.</string>
    <string name="pubic_mound_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s pubic area. Caress it with light circular motions or smooth strokes. Use oils or lotions to enhance the sensations. Explore the texture and shape while tuning in to your partner\'s responses.</string>
    <string name="pubic_mound_kiss_action">%, gently kiss and caress %\'s pubic area. Soft, playful kisses can be especially arousing.</string>
    <string name="pubic_mound_lick_action">%, use your tongue to stimulate %\'s pubic area. Gentle licking can heighten sensitivity and arousal.</string>
    <string name="pubic_mound_use_accessories_0_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to stimulate %\'s pubic area. Glide it over the surface to introduce variety and awaken new sensations.</string>
    <string name="pubic_mound_use_accessories_1_action">%, use special toys such as small vibrators or clitoral stimulators to stimulate %\'s pubic area. These can add variety and create new, exciting sensations.</string>
    <string name="pubic_mound_ice_action">%, gently glide an ice cube over %\'s pubic area to stimulate the skin. Playing with temperature can intensify sensations and heighten arousal.</string>
    <string name="clitoris_massage_0_action">%, gently stroke and massage %\'s clitoris. Light circular motions and delicate caresses can create pleasant sensations. Use a generous amount of water-based lubricant to avoid discomfort.</string>
    <string name="clitoris_massage_1_action">%, massage %\'s clitoris using gentle pressure and circular motions. Try different techniques and levels of intensity to discover what brings your partner the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="clitoris_kiss_action">%, gently kiss %\'s clitoris. Experiment with different rhythms to find what gives your partner the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="clitoris_lick_action">%, use your tongue to caress %\'s clitoris. Try different techniques, such as circular motions, light pressure, and gentle sucking, to enhance stimulation. Oral play can be intensely arousing.</string>
    <string name="clitoris_bite_action">%, gently nibble on %\'s clitoris to provide subtle stimulation. Always pay attention to your partner\'s preferences and comfort.</string>
    <string name="clitoris_use_accessories_action">%, use clitoral stimulators, vibrators, or massagers to pleasure %. Be sure to use plenty of water-based lubricant and stay attentive to your partner\'s reactions.</string>
    <string name="clitoris_itself_action">%, invite % to stimulate her clitoris herself. This can be a deeply intimate and arousing experience.</string>
    <string name="g_spot_massage_action">%, insert one or two fingers into %\'s vagina, or use a specially curved toy designed for G-spot stimulation. Apply water-based lubricant to moisten the area and ensure smooth movement. Locate a small bulge on the front vaginal wall, then gently massage the G-spot with circular motions, varying rhythm and intensity.</string>
    <string name="g_spot_itself_action">%, invite % to stimulate her G-spot herself using fingers or a curved toy. This can be a deeply intimate and arousing experience.</string>
    <string name="anus_massage_action">%, apply water-based lubricant and begin with gentle finger caresses around %\'s anus. Gradually explore slow and careful penetration with a finger. Always be cautious, observe your partner\'s reaction, and respect his preferences and boundaries.</string>
    <string name="anus_use_accessories_0_action">%, use anal toys such as plugs or vibrators to stimulate %\'s anus. Always use plenty of water-based lubricant, and begin with smaller-sized toys to help your partner feel safe and comfortable.</string>
    <string name="anus_use_accessories_1_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to stimulate %\'s anus. Gentle, teasing strokes can feel deeply sensual and arousing.</string>
    <string name="anus_kiss_action">%, gently kiss %\'s anus. Make sure the area is clean and lubricated to ensure comfort and hygiene.</string>
    <string name="anus_lick_action">%, gently lick %\'s anus. Ensure the area is clean and lubricated for comfort and hygiene. Rimming (anal licking) can be highly erotic and deeply arousing for some people.</string>
    <string name="anus_ice_action">%, use an ice cube to stimulate %\'s anus. Be cautious, observe your partner\'s reaction, and respect his boundaries and comfort levels.</string>
    <string name="anus_itself_action">%, % can stimulate his anus on his own using fingers or anal toys, while you watch and offer support. Mutual self-pleasure can be a deeply intimate and arousing experience.</string>
    <string name="buttocks_massage_action">%, massage %\'s buttocks using circular motions, gentle pressure, stroking, light slaps, rubbing, pinching, or deep kneading. Massage oils or lotions can enhance stimulation in this sensitive area.</string>
    <string name="buttocks_kiss_action">%, kiss %\'s buttocks. Playful kisses can awaken arousal and pleasure.</string>
    <string name="buttocks_lick_action">%, lick %\'s buttocks, giving extra attention to the area around the anus if your partner enjoys it.</string>
    <string name="buttocks_bite_action">%, gently nibble on %\'s buttocks. Pay close attention to your partner\'s response to ensure it remains pleasurable.</string>
    <string name="buttocks_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to stimulate %\'s buttocks. Gently glide it over the skin to introduce variety and new sensations, focusing especially on the area around the anus if desired.</string>
    <string name="buttocks_ice_action">%, gently glide an ice cube over %\'s buttocks to offer cool contrast and awaken new sensations.</string>
    <string name="glans_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s glans. Try different techniques, such as light pressure, gentle squeezing, up-and-down strokes, or circular motions. Use water-based lubricant to keep the area moisturized and ensure smooth hand movements.</string>
    <string name="glans_kiss_action">%, gently kiss %\'s glans. Use water-based lubricant to keep the area soft and ensure comfortable movements.</string>
    <string name="glans_lick_action">%, gently lick %\'s glans with your tongue. Experiment with different movements and rhythms, such as slow circles or tip-focused strokes, to discover what brings your partner the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="glans_bite_action">%, gently nibble on %\'s glans. Watch your partner\'s reaction closely and adjust based on his response.</string>
    <string name="glans_suck_action">%, gently suck on %\'s glans, maintaining soft, consistent pressure for maximum pleasure.</string>
    <string name="glans_use_accessories_action">%, use toys such as penis massagers or vibrators to stimulate %\'s glans. Always apply water-based lubricant for comfort and enhanced sensation.</string>
    <string name="glans_ice_action">%, gently glide an ice cube over %\'s glans. Temperature play can create surprising and exciting sensations.</string>
    <string name="glans_itself_action">%, let % stimulate his own glans. Be attentive to his preferences and reactions, and support him throughout the experience.</string>
    <string name="scrotum_and_testicles_massage_action">%, massage %\'s scrotum. Gently caress it with light circular motions, soft strokes, or gentle squeezes. Use plenty of water-based lubricant and stay attentive to your partner\'s responses and preferences.</string>
    <string name="scrotum_and_testicles_kiss_action">%, gently kiss %\'s scrotum to offer a delicate and intimate sensation.</string>
    <string name="scrotum_and_testicles_lick_action">%, use your tongue to stimulate %\'s scrotum. Lick and caress it with soft, deliberate motions. Explore different rhythms to discover what brings your partner the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="scrotum_and_testicles_bite_action">%, gently nibble or bite %\'s scrotum. Be attentive to your partner\'s responses and comfort level.</string>
    <string name="scrotum_and_testicles_suck_action">%, gently suck %\'s scrotum and testicles. Experiment with various rhythms and techniques to discover what gives your partner the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="scrotum_and_testicles_use_accessories_0_action">%, use toys like massagers or vibrators to stimulate %\'s scrotum and testicles. Always apply water-based lubricant for smooth sensations.</string>
    <string name="scrotum_and_testicles_use_accessories_1_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to stimulate %\'s scrotum. Gentle strokes can awaken sensitivity and add excitement.</string>
    <string name="perineum_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s perineum. Caress this sensitive area with light circular motions or up-and-down strokes. Pay close attention to your partner\'s reactions and preferences regarding intensity and pressure.</string>
    <string name="perineum_lick_action">%, use your tongue to stimulate %\'s perineum. Caress this area with soft, deliberate tongue movements. Experiment with different rhythms to discover what brings your partner the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="perineum_use_accessories_action">%, use accessories like feathers, vibrators, or massagers to stimulate %\'s perineum. Always use plenty of water-based lubricant and stay attuned to your partner\'s reactions.</string>
    <string name="prostate_massage_action">%, apply water-based lubricant and gently insert your fingers into %\'s anus. Massage the prostate with light circular motions along the front wall of the rectum. Always be careful, gentle, and attentive to your partner\'s comfort.</string>
    <string name="prostate_use_accessories_action">%, use prostate massagers or vibrators to stimulate %\'s prostate. Always use plenty of water-based lubricant and follow the toy\'s instructions carefully.</string>
    <string name="prostate_itself_action">%, let % explore prostate stimulation on his own while you offer support and presence. This can be a deeply intimate and exciting experience for both of you.</string>
    <string name="penis_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s penis. Use plenty of water-based lubricant for optimal comfort. Experiment with different rhythms and motions—such as up-and-down strokes, light touches, and gentle squeezes—to discover what brings your partner the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="penis_kiss_action">%, softly kiss %\'s penis, moving from the base to the tip with tender kisses.</string>
    <string name="penis_suck_action">%, gently suck %\'s penis. Try different rhythms and techniques, like slow up-and-down motions or deeper movements, to discover what gives your partner the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="penis_lick_action">%, lick %\'s penis. Run your tongue from the base to the tip, using circular motions or gentle strokes to vary the sensation.</string>
    <string name="penis_use_accessories_0_action">%, use penis massagers or vibrators to stimulate %\'s penis. Always apply plenty of water-based lubricant to ensure smooth and pleasurable sensations.</string>
    <string name="penis_use_accessories_1_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to stimulate %\'s penis. Gentle touches can awaken extra sensations and enhance arousal.</string>
    <string name="penis_ice_action">%, gently glide an ice cube over %\'s penis. Temperature play can be surprisingly stimulating and exciting.</string>
    <string name="penis_itself_action">%, let % massage his own penis while you observe and support him. Pay close attention to his reactions and preferences.</string>
    <string name="nipples_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s nipples and the surrounding area. Use soft strokes, circular motions, and light pinches. Oils or lotions can enhance the sensations and make the experience even more pleasurable.</string>
    <string name="nipples_kiss_action">%, gently kiss %\'s nipples with slow, tender pressure.</string>
    <string name="nipples_lick_action">%, softly lick %\'s nipples and the area around them, varying speed and pressure for added pleasure.</string>
    <string name="nipples_bite_action">%, lightly nibble on %\'s nipples, staying gentle and attentive to your partner\'s response.</string>
    <string name="nipples_ice_action">%, glide an ice cube around %\'s nipples or gently press it to the skin to create a cool, stimulating sensation.</string>
    <string name="nipples_use_accessories_0_action">%, use a massager, vibrator, or adjustable clamp to stimulate %\'s nipples. These accessories can create exciting new sensations and deepen the sensual experience.</string>
    <string name="nipples_use_accessories_1_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to tease %\'s nipples. This can awaken extra excitement and arousal.</string>
    <string name="nipples_suck_action">%, gently suck on %\'s nipples, alternating with light licks or kisses to increase stimulation.</string>
    <string name="small_of_the_back_massage_action">%, massage %\'s lower back. Try different techniques such as circular motions, gentle pressure, or light pinching to help your partner relax. Using oil or lotion can also make the massage more sensual and arousing.</string>
    <string name="small_of_the_back_kiss_action">%, kiss %\'s lower back. Explore the area with soft, lingering kisses while observing your partner\'s reactions.</string>
    <string name="small_of_the_back_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to slowly trace along %\'s lower back, awakening delicate sensations.</string>
    <string name="small_of_the_back_ice_action">%, gently glide an ice cube along %\'s lower back to introduce a cool, thrilling contrast.</string>
    <string name="armpits_massage_action">%, gently massage %\'s armpits. Use light circular motions or soft strokes to stimulate this sensitive area. Applying oil or lotion can make the experience more sensual and arousing.</string>
    <string name="armpits_kiss_action">%, kiss %\'s armpits with your lips. Playful kisses and soft caresses can be unexpectedly arousing.</string>
    <string name="armpits_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to lightly tease %\'s armpits, adding a playful and stimulating sensation.</string>
    <string name="armpits_ice_action">%, slowly glide an ice cube over %\'s armpits to awaken new sensations and add a thrilling chill to the experience.</string>
    <string name="inner_arms_massage_action">%, gently massage the inner side of %\'s arms. Use soft strokes, circular motions, and light pinching to enhance stimulation. Massage oil or lotion can intensify the sensations and increase arousal.</string>
    <string name="inner_arms_kiss_action">%, caress the inner side of %\'s arms with soft kisses or light nibbling. Playful touches in this area can be surprisingly arousing.</string>
    <string name="inner_arms_lick_action">%, use your tongue to stimulate the inner side of %\'s arms. Light licking in this sensitive area can create waves of pleasure and anticipation.</string>
    <string name="inner_arms_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to gently tease the inner side of %\'s arms and spark new sensations.</string>
    <string name="inner_arms_ice_action">%, glide an ice cube along the inner side of %\'s arms. This cool contrast can introduce exciting variety and heighten sensitivity.</string>
    <string name="inner_wrist_massage_action">%, gently massage the inner side of %\'s wrists. Using oil or lotion can enhance the sensations and add a sensual touch to the experience.</string>
    <string name="inner_wrist_kiss_action">%, caress the inner side of %\'s wrists with playful kisses. Gentle touches in this sensitive area can spark arousal.</string>
    <string name="inner_wrist_lick_action">%, gently lick the inner side of %\'s wrists. Soft tongue movements here can awaken pleasure and build anticipation.</string>
    <string name="inner_wrist_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to gently stimulate the inner side of %\'s wrists. This can introduce variety and spark new sensations.</string>
    <string name="inner_wrist_ice_action">%, glide an ice cube along the inner side of %\'s wrists. Temperature play here can create an exciting and refreshing contrast.</string>
    <string name="palm_of_hands_and_fingertips_massage_action">%, massage %\'s palms with gentle pressure and circular motions. This can create soothing sensations and deep relaxation.</string>
    <string name="palm_of_hands_and_fingertips_kiss_action">%, kiss %\'s palms gently with your lips. Don\'t forget the fingertips—touch them with slow, tender kisses.</string>
    <string name="palm_of_hands_and_fingertips_lick_action">%, gently lick %\'s palms and fingertips to heighten arousal and offer a unique sensual experience.</string>
    <string name="palm_of_hands_and_fingertips_suck_action">%, softly suck on %\'s fingertips. This can intensify arousal and create a teasing, sensual moment.</string>
    <string name="palm_of_hands_and_fingertips_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to stimulate %\'s palms and fingertips. Light touches can introduce new sensations and enhance arousal.</string>
    <string name="behind_the_knee_massage_action">%, gently massage the area behind %\'s knees using light circular motions, soft pressure, or gentle pinches. Pay close attention to your partner\'s reactions and preferences. Applying massage oil or lotion can enhance the sensations and add to the arousal.</string>
    <string name="behind_the_knee_kiss_action">%, kiss the area behind %\'s knees, adding playful nibbles with your lips. Gentle, erotic kisses in this sensitive spot can be highly arousing.</string>
    <string name="behind_the_knee_lick_action">%, gently lick the area behind %\'s knees to awaken pleasurable and unexpected sensations.</string>
    <string name="behind_the_knee_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to tease the area behind %\'s knees. Light touches can provide extra pleasure and enhance arousal.</string>
    <string name="lips_massage_action">%, gently run your fingertips along %\'s lips. You can also use food, like fruit or ice cream—glide it over her lips and let her taste it slowly. This adds playful intimacy and awakens new sensations.</string>
    <string name="lips_kiss_action">%, experiment with different types of kisses—gentle, passionate, playful, or barely-there lip touches. Vary the rhythm and intensity to explore what excites % the most.</string>
    <string name="lips_lick_action">%, use the tip of your tongue to slowly caress %\'s lips with gentle licks or circular motions. Explore what types of touches bring her the most pleasure.</string>
    <string name="lips_bite_action">%, gently nibble on %\'s lips to enhance stimulation and awaken new sensations. Many find soft biting or teasing nibbles on the lips highly arousing.</string>
    <string name="lips_ice_action">%, slowly run an ice cube over %\'s lips. The contrast in temperature can awaken new sensations and spark arousal.</string>
    <string name="neck_massage_0_action">%, massage %\'s neck using gentle pressure and circular motions to relax the muscles and create pleasant sensations. Massage oils or lotions can make the experience even more enjoyable.</string>
    <string name="neck_massage_1_action">%, vary your touch and pressure based on %\'s preferences. Use your fingertips for light caresses, or apply gentle pressure to different parts of the neck. Don\'t forget to use oil or lotion to heighten arousal.</string>
    <string name="neck_kiss_action">%, kiss or gently nibble %\'s neck. Playful touches in this sensitive area can trigger waves of pleasure and arousal.</string>
    <string name="neck_lick_action">%, slowly lick %\'s neck. This can evoke deep erotic sensations and intensify the moment.</string>
    <string name="neck_use_accessories_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to tease %\'s neck. Glide it along the skin to introduce new, tingling sensations.</string>
    <string name="neck_ice_action">%, glide an ice cube along %\'s neck. The contrast of cold against warm skin can awaken new sensations and heighten arousal.</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh_massage_0_action">%, gently massage %\'s inner thigh. Soft, caressing touches can create deeply pleasurable sensations and spark arousal. Using oils or lotions can make the experience even more sensual.</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh_massage_1_action">%, vary your touch and pressure on %\'s inner thigh. Some enjoy soft, delicate caresses, while others respond better to firmer, more vigorous strokes. Don\'t forget to use oil or lotion to enhance arousal.</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh_kiss_action">%, caress %\'s inner thigh with your lips—kiss it gently or playfully nibble to build anticipation. This area is often very sensitive and highly arousing.</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh_lick_action">%, use your tongue to explore %\'s inner thigh. Gentle licks along this sensitive area can awaken pleasure and arousal.</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh_bite_action">%, gently nibble on the outer part of %\'s thigh to add playful stimulation and deepen arousal.</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh_use_accessories_0_action">%, use a feather or another soft accessory to tease %\'s inner thigh. Light strokes can introduce variety and awaken new sensations.</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh_use_accessories_1_action">%, use a massager, vibrator, or similar accessory to stimulate %\'s outer thigh. This can create unforgettable sensations and heighten your partner\'s arousal.</string>
    <string name="inner_thigh_ice_action">%, gently glide an ice cube along %\'s inner thigh. The cool contrast can heighten sensitivity and spark extra excitement.</string>
    <string name="bottom_of_feet_and_toes_massage_0_action">%, massage %\'s feet using circular motions and gentle pressure, moving from the base of the toes down to the heel. Focus on key points to relax and stimulate. Using oil or lotion can enhance relaxation and intensify pleasure.</string>
    <string name="bottom_of_feet_and_toes_massage_1_action">%, gently stroke %\'s feet and toes with your fingertips. This soothing gesture can feel incredibly comforting and intimate.</string>
    <string name="bottom_of_feet_and_toes_kiss_action">%, kiss %\'s feet and toes slowly and sensually to provide extra stimulation and playful excitement.</string>
    <string name="bottom_of_feet_and_toes_lick_action">%, use your tongue to stimulate %\'s feet and toes. Gentle licking can evoke pleasant tingles and awaken new sensations.</string>
    <string name="bottom_of_feet_and_toes_suck_action">%, softly suck on %\'s toes. This can be both deeply relaxing and surprisingly arousing for your partner.</string>
    <string name="bottom_of_feet_and_toes_use_accessories_action">%, stimulate %\'s feet using feathers, massage balls, rollers, or other accessories. These tools can deepen sensation and introduce playful variety.</string>
    <string name="bottom_of_feet_and_toes_ice_action">%, glide an ice cube over %\'s feet, applying light pressure to key points. The cool sensation can relax and awaken heightened sensitivity.</string>

    <string name="about_app_description">\t\tWelcome to LoveIn - the mobile application designed to bring pleasure, enjoyment, and a new
        experience to your intimate life! LoveIn is a unique experience for partners, exploring new emotional facets and
        intimate scenarios for those who seek to strengthen their relationship and improve their bond with their
        partner.\n\n
        \t\tApp features:\n\n
        • Personalized experience: With LoveIn, you can create your character by choosing your gender and name, and also
        define your preferred erogenous zones. This allows you to enjoy unique and intimate moments, specially created
        for you and your partner.\n\n
        • Play as a couple or with a larger group: LoveIn doesn\'t limit you in the number of participants. You can play
        as a couple, creating cozy and romantic moments, or add friends for fun, exciting, and arousing games that will
        reveal new aspects of your intimate life.\n\n
        • Variety of actions: Press the "Play" button, and you will be presented with a card describing an action that
        one of the players must perform towards the other, focusing on a random erogenous zone chosen by the second
        player. This will expand your intimate horizons and bring pleasure and joy to your mutual relationship.\n\n
        • Strengthening connection and trust: LoveIn is created to support open and honest communication between
        partners, revealing new facets of their relationship and increasing the level of trust and closeness.\n\n

        \t\tJoin LoveIn and discover unexplored facets of pleasure and enjoyment in your intimate life. Immerse yourself in
        a unique experience created with love and care, and share moments of passion and intimacy with your partner or
        friends. Enjoy boldness and novelty in your relationship with LoveIn.
    </string>

    <string name="finish_title">The study is complete</string>
    <string name="finish_description">The study of erogenous zones is complete. You can go back and start over.</string>
    <string name="ok_button">OK</string>
    <string name="download_body_map_and_rating">Download Body Map and Ratings</string>
    <string name="open_next_card">Open next card</string>
</resources>
